<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="url_load_unsuccessful_message">"[Ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ îšñ'ţ çöññéçţéð ţö å ḿöɓîļé ðåţå šéŕVîçé. Ţö Vîéŵ ţĥîš îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ ñöŵ, ĝö ţö %s îñ å ŵéɓ ɓŕöŵšéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="activation_text">[Ţöûçĥ <b>ÅçţîVåţé</b>" ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé šéŕVîçé ñöŵ. (Îţ ḿåý ţåķé å çöûþļé öƒ ḿîñûţéš.)

Öŕ ţöûçĥ "<b>Šķîþ</b> ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ ûšîñĝ å Ŵî-Fî çöññéçţîöñ îñšţéåð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="activation_skip_confirmation">"[Ûñţîļ ýöû åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå šéŕVîçé, ḿöšţ öƒ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ'š ƒéåţûŕéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ.

Îƒ ýöû þŕéƒéŕ ţö šķîþ ñöŵ, ýöû çåñ åçţîVåţé ļåţéŕ îñ Šýšţéḿ Šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="activation_failure_text">"[Ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå šéŕVîçé çöûļðñ'ţ ɓé åçţîVåţéð. Ţĥîš ḿåý ɓé å ţéḿþöŕåŕý þŕöɓļéḿ.

Îƒ ýöû þŕéƒéŕ ţö šķîþ ñöŵ, ɓé šûŕé ţö åçţîVåţé ļåţéŕ îñ Šýšţéḿ Šéţţîñĝš. Ûñţîļ ýöû åçţîVåţé, ḿöšţ öƒ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ'š ƒéåţûŕéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="activation_failure_text_gen">"[Ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå šéŕVîçé çöûļðñ'ţ ɓé åçţîVåţéð. Ţĥîš ḿåý ɓé å ţéḿþöŕåŕý þŕöɓļéḿ, åñð ḿåý ɓé šöļVéð ɓý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ţĥé ţåɓļéţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one]"</string>
    <string name="activation_spc_failure_text">[Ţĥéŕé ŵåš åñ éŕŕöŕ ţĥåţ ŕéQûîŕéš šĥûţţîñĝ ðöŵñ åñð ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ ɓéƒöŕé ýöû çåñ ḿåķé åñöţĥéŕ åçţîVåţîöñ åţţéḿþţ. Ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ ŵîļļ šĥûţ ðöŵñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý îñ 60 šéçöñðš, öŕ ýöû çåñ ţöûçĥ <b>Šĥûţ ðöŵñ ñöŵ</b>".

Öñçé ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ îš šĥûţ ðöŵñ, þŕéšš ţĥé Þöŵéŕ ɓûţţöñ ţö ŕéšţåŕţ îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_message">[Ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ îš šéţ ûþ åñð ŕéåðý ţö ûšé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="sim_missing_text">[Ţö îñšéŕţ ýöûŕ ŠÎḾ çåŕð, ŕéåð ţĥé îñšţŕûçţîöñš ţĥåţ çåḿé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
</resources>
