<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_picker_no_apps_found">No apps found.</string>
    <string name="apps_permissions_described_v2">"Only popular, free iOS® apps can be matched to Android apps. Most in-app purchases won’t transfer. You can find more apps in the Play Store once setup has been completed.

You may need to give some apps upfront permission to access specific capabilities or information on your device. Permissions are organised into permission groups. By selecting to install these apps, you accept the permissions that are part of each group. A description of each permissions group is provided below.

Some apps may not require accepting permissions upfront. When you use one of these apps, you can allow or deny individual permission before the app uses that type of data.

^1"</string>
    <string name="apps_permissions_disclaimer_v2">By installing each app, you agree with its permissions. <annotation id="apps_permissions_learn_more">Find out more</annotation></string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary">Back up app data, Wi‑Fi passwords and other settings to Google Drive</string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary_full">"Automatically back up device data (such as Wi-Fi passwords and call history) and app data (such as settings and files stored by apps) remotely.

When you turn on automatic backup, device and app data is regularly saved remotely. App data can be any data that an app has saved (based on developer settings), including potentially sensitive data such as contacts, messages and photos."</string>
    <string name="backup_erase_dialog_message">Stop backing up your Wi‑Fi passwords, bookmarks, other settings and app data, plus delete all copies on Google Drive?</string>
    <string name="backup_opt_in_backup_auth_setup_wizard_services_backup_dialog_text">"When you turn on automatic backup:

 ● Device settings and app data are periodically saved to a private folder in Google Drive. App data can be any data that an app has saved (based on developer settings), including potentially sensitive data such as contacts, messages and photos.

 Large files or files developers have chosen to exclude from the service, will not be backed up.

 ● Photos and video recordings from this device are synced with your Google Photos library to search, edit, delete and share from any of your devices.

 By default, full resolution photos and videos are uploaded. These do not count against your Drive storage quota.

 ● Contacts and associated data from this device are synced to Google Contacts. You can use the Google Contacts app to search, edit, delete and share contacts from any of your devices.

 ● Calendar entries and associated data from this device are synced to Google Calendar. You can use the Google Calendar app to search, edit, delete and share entries from any of your devices.

 Backup data will not count towards your Drive storage quota."</string>
    <string name="backup_opt_in_backup_auth_setup_wizard_services_backup_dialog_text_no_photos">"When you turn on automatic backup:

 ● Device settings and app data are periodically saved to a private folder in Google Drive. App data can be any data that an app has saved (based on developer settings), including potentially sensitive data such as contacts, messages and photos.

 Large files or files developers have chosen to exclude from the service, will not be backed up.

 ● Contacts and associated data from this device are synced to Google Contacts. You can use the Google Contacts app to search, edit, delete and share contacts from any of your devices.

 ● Calendar entries and associated data from this device are synced to Google Calendar. You can use the Google Calendar app to search, edit, delete and share entries from any of your devices.

 Backup data will not count towards your Drive storage quota."</string>
    <string name="backup_opt_in_backup_description_extra">Calendar, contacts, photos and videos are synced to your Google account and may be used across services.</string>
    <string name="backup_opt_in_backup_description_v2">Automatic backup ensures that you can easily restore or switch phones at any time. <annotation id="backup_opt_in_learn_more">Find out more</annotation></string>
    <string name="backup_opt_in_backup_disable_confirmation_description_v2">"This will turn off backup for:

Apps and app data
Call history
Device settings
Photos and videos
SMS

Calendar and contacts will continue to sync to your Google account. When setup is complete, you can change sync settings by going to "<annotation id="backup_opt_in_settings_instructions">Settings > Accounts > Google</annotation>.</string>
    <string name="common_add_account_label">Add an account.</string>
    <string name="common_connected_apps_settings_title">Apps connected</string>
    <string name="common_connecting">Connecting …</string>
    <string name="common_get_started">Get started.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wrong_architecture_text">Google Play services have been installed with an architecture (%1$s) that is different from your device architecture (%2$s).</string>
    <string name="common_learn_more">Find out more</string>
    <string name="common_loading">Loading …</string>
    <string name="common_missing_url_viewer">Missing viewer to show an external URL.</string>
    <string name="common_no_thanks">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="common_open_source_licenses">Open-source licences</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign In</string>
    <string name="common_terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="common_url_load_unsuccessful_message_wifi_only">"Your Android device isn't connected to a Wi-Fi network. To view this information now, visit %s via a web browser."</string>
    <string name="copy_confirmation_description">You’ll be copying data, such as your Google Account and apps, to your new phone</string>
    <string name="d2d_migration_canceled_on_source">Copying cancelled</string>
    <string name="data_copied_fragment_description">Your data has been copied to your new phone. You can unplug the cable.</string>
    <string name="device_not_supported_fragment_retry_description">Make sure that your old phone is unlocked, then disconnect and reconnect the cable</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_apps_in_backup">Backed-up app data</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_apps_loading">Loading …</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_content_calendar_dialog_message">Events created in Google Calendar will be synced across all devices that are signed into your Google account.</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_content_contacts_dialog_message">Contacts created in Google Contacts will be synced across all devices that are signed into your Google account.</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_content_devicesettings_dialog_message">Backup includes device configuration, such as wallpaper, Wi-Fi passwords and default apps.</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_content_status_never">Waiting to back up</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_disabled_backuplist_no_photos">"Backup includes:
\u0009– Apps and apps data
\u0009– Call history
\u0009– Device settings (including Wi-Fi passwords)
\u0009– Google Calendar
\u0009– Google Contacts
\u0009– SMS"</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_disabled_detailedinfo">"Google Calendar, Google Contacts, photos and videos are synced to your Google account and may be used across services.

Sync may be enabled even if backup is turned off. Sync settings can be changed in Settings > Accounts > Google."</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_disabled_detailedinfo_no_photos">"Google Calendar and Google Contacts are synced to your Google account and may be used across services.

Sync may be enabled even if backup is turned off. Sync settings can be changed in Settings > Accounts > Google."</string>
    <string name="drive_backup_disabled_introduction">Automatic backup ensures that you can easily restore or switch phones at any time.</string>
    <string name="encryption_warning_fragment_description">"Backup encryption is turned on for your iPhone® device. If you didn’t turn this on yourself, it might have been turned on by your IT admin.

Only photos, music and videos can be copied over. For more information, visit "<b>g.co/datatransferhelp</b>.</string>
    <string name="fragment_usb_cant_find_adapter">I can’t find the adaptor</string>
    <string name="fragment_usb_connect_adapter_with_cable_description">"Find the Quick Switch Adaptor that came in the same box as your ^1.

Plug the cable into the adaptor."</string>
    <string name="fragment_usb_connect_adapter_with_cable_title">Connect the adaptor &amp; cable</string>
    <string name="fragment_usb_connect_both_phones_description_v2">Unlock your old phone, then plug the adaptor into this phone.</string>
    <string name="fragment_usb_legacy_description">"This is the fastest way to bring over the most data.

Find the adaptor in the box and plug it into your new phone. Connect the phones using a cable, then unlock your old phone."</string>
    <string name="fragment_waiting_title">Just a second…</string>
    <string name="i_message_dialog_message">"To keep receiving SMS messages from iPhone® device users, you'll need to turn off iMessage®.

Visit "<b>g.co/iMessageHelp</b> for instructions.</string>
    <string name="ios_connected_fragment_description">"On the next screen, you can sign in to your Google account, or create a new one.

If you don’t add your Google account, your iOS Calendar® events won’t transfer."</string>
    <string name="ios_photos_dialog_message">"Photos stored in iCloud® can't be copied.

To bring these photos to your ^1, install the Google Photos app on your iPhone® device, and turn on Back up &amp; sync. Visit "<b>g.co/datatransferhelp</b> for more instructions.</string>
    <string name="manage_data_label">Google account</string>
    <string name="permgrouplab_phone">Telephone</string>
    <string name="permgrouplab_sensors">Body sensors</string>
    <string name="photo_backup_configure_account_default_summary">No account is currently storing backed-up photos</string>
    <string name="restore_choice_data_disclaimer_bottom_android">Copied contacts will be saved to your Google account.</string>
    <string name="restore_choice_data_disclaimer_bottom_ios">Copied contacts and calendars will be saved to your Google account.</string>
    <string name="restore_choice_data_disclaimer_v2">Some of your data might not be copied to your ^1. <annotation id="restore_choice_data_disclaimer_learn_more">Find out more</annotation></string>
    <string name="restore_choice_learn_more_android">"Some data from your old phone can't be copied automatically:

 ● Downloads (such as PDF files)

 ● Photos, videos &amp; music stored in hidden folders

 ● Photos, videos &amp; music received via text message

 ● Apps that aren't from the Google Play Store

 ● App data (if the app doesn't use Android backup)

 ● Certain device settings

 ● Accounts other than Google accounts (and any associated data)

 ● Contacts &amp; calendars synced to services other than Google

 ● Ringtones

 For more details and help copying some of this data, visit g.co/datatransferhelp."</string>
    <string name="restore_choice_learn_more_ios">"Some data from your old phone can't be copied automatically:

 ● Apps &amp; app data

 ● Photos where an original isn't stored on your phone (for example, if the Optimise Storage setting is on, original photos are stored in iCloud®)

 ● Files &amp; documents stored in iCloud®

 ● Device settings (such as Wi-Fi passwords &amp; wallpaper)

 ● Music protected with Digital Rights Management (DRM) protection (for example, iTunes® music purchased before April 2009 or music downloaded for offline listening in a music streaming app)

 ● Accounts other than Google Accounts (and any associated data)

 ● Contacts &amp; calendars synced to services other than Google or iCloud®

 ● Bookmarks from Safari®

 iMessage® attachments will be available in Google Photos > Device folders > Message attachments.

 For more details and help copying some of this data, visit g.co/datatransferhelp."</string>
    <string name="restore_error_message">Something went wrong with restoration. Sorry.</string>
    <string name="restore_selected_size_and_device_space_text"><annotation id="selected_size">^1</annotation> ^2 / ^3</string>
    <string name="source_copying_description">The data that you chose is being copied to your new phone</string>
    <string name="source_success_screen_title">Finished!</string>
    <string name="target_smart_device_timeout_description">"If you'd prefer, you could try adding your account manually"</string>
    <string name="transfer_finished_fragment_title">Adding the finishing touches...</string>
    <string name="transfer_summary_icloud_photos_warning_v2">"Some of your photos weren't copied. "<annotation id="transfer_summary_learn_more">Find out more</annotation></string>
    <string name="transfer_summary_partial">%1$s / %2$s copied</string>
    <string name="trust_instructions_trademark_disclaimer">iPhone, iPad, iOS, iMessage, iCloud, Safari and iTunes are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the US and other countries.</string>
</resources>
