<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_label">[Ĝööĝļé Šîĝñ Îñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="settings_ok">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_on">[Öñ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_yes">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="settings_no">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="settings_skip">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="enable">[Éñåɓļé one two]</string>
    <string name="disable">[Ðîšåɓļé one two]</string>
    <string name="system_email_address">[Éḿåîļ åððŕéšš one two]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_overview_one_first_run">[Ŵéļçöḿé ţö ýöûŕ ñéŵ Åñðŕöîð Ţν ðéVîçé þöŵéŕéð ɓý Ĝööĝļé. Åñðŕöîð Ţν ļéţš ýöû ĝéţ åþþš ƒŕöḿ ţĥé Þļåý Šţöŕé åñð çåšţ çöñţéñţ ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ þĥöñé ţö ţĥé Ţν. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_overview_one">[Åñðŕöîð Ţν ļéţš ýöû ĝéţ åþþš ƒŕöḿ ţĥé Þļåý Šţöŕé åñð çåšţ çöñţéñţ ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ þĥöñé ţö ţĥé Ţν. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_overview_two">[βý šîĝñîñĝ îñ ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé, ýöû’ļļ ĝéţ þéŕšöñåļîžéð ŕéçöḿḿéñðåţîöñš öñ ţĥé ĥöḿé šçŕééñ, åñð Ýöûţûɓé, Ĝööĝļé Þļåý, åñð öţĥéŕ åþþš îñšţåļļéð ƒŕöḿ ţĥé Þļåý Šţöŕé ŵîļļ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ĝéţ ûþðåţéð ţö ţĥé ļåţéšţ ƒéåţûŕéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]</string>
    <string name="google">[Ĝööĝļé one two]</string>
    <string name="account_i_have_an_account">[Î ĥåVé åñ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_use_second_device">[Ûšé ýöûŕ þĥöñé öŕ ļåþţöþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_create_account">[Çŕéåţé åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_try_again">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_enter_first_name">[Éñţéŕ ýöûŕ ƒîŕšţ ñåḿé one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_enter_name">[Ýöûŕ ñåḿé îš ûšéð ţö þéŕšöñåļîžé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð Ĝööĝļé ŠéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="account_enter_last_name">[Éñţéŕ ýöûŕ ļåšţ ñåḿé one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_loading_setup_pin">[ŔéţŕîéVîñĝ ÞÎÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="bad_name_text">"[Çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥîš ñåḿé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="invalid_name_text">"[Ýöû çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥîš ñåḿé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé+ ɓéçåûšé îţ çöñţåîñš îñVåļîð çĥåŕåçţéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="invalid_nickname_text">"[Ýöû çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥîš ñåḿé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé+ ɓéçåûšé îţ çöñţåîñš îñVåļîð çĥåŕåçţéŕš. Ţŕýîñĝ ţö ûšé å ñîçķñåḿé, þŕéVîöûš ñåḿé, öŕ ţîţļé¿ Ýöû çåñ åðð ţĥéḿ ţö ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé åƒţéŕ ýöû ĵöîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="invalid_other_text">"[Ţĥîš ñåḿé çåñ'ţ ɓé ûšéð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé+. one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="account_choose_user_name">"[Ĥéļļö %1$s
Çĥööšé å ûšéŕñåḿé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_enter_custom_name">[Éñţéŕ å çûšţöḿ ñåḿé one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_enter_username">[Éñţéŕ å ûšéŕñåḿé one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_enter_username">"[Ýöû'ļļ ûšé ţĥîš ñåḿé ţö šîĝñ îñţö ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. Ýöû çåñ ûšé ļéţţéŕš, ñûḿɓéŕš, åñð þéŕîöðš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="account_create_password">[Çŕéåţé å þåššŵöŕð one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_create_password">"[Ûšé åţ ļéåšţ 8 çĥåŕåçţéŕš. Ðöñ'ţ ŕéûšé þåššŵöŕðš, öŕ šöḿéţĥîñĝ ţöö öɓVîöûš ļîķé ýöûŕ þéţ'š ñåḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="account_confirm_password">[Çöñƒîŕḿ ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_confirm_password">[Ḿåķé šûŕé ýöû ţýþéð ŵĥåţ ýöû ţĥöûĝĥţ ýöû ţýþéð. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="account_recovery_email_address">[ŔéçöVéŕý éḿåîļ åððŕéšš one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_recovery_email_address">[Îƒ ýöû éVéŕ ļöšé ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð, ýöû çåñ åñšŵéŕ å šéçûŕîţý Qûéšţîöñ åñð ĥåVé å ŕéšéţ ļîñķ éḿåîļéð ţö å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ åððŕéšš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="account_choose_security_question">[Çĥööšé å šéçûŕîţý Qûéšţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_answer_security_question">[Éñţéŕ åñ åñšŵéŕ ţö ýöûŕ šéçûŕîţý Qûéšţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="account_accept">[Åççéþţ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_view_terms">[νîéŵ Ĝööĝļé Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_view_privacy_policy">[νîéŵ Ĝööĝļé ÞŕîVåçý Þöļîçý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_view_play_terms">[νîéŵ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_dont_create_account">"[Ðöñ'ţ çŕéåţé åççöûñţ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_desc_tos_title">[Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé &amp; ÞŕîVåçý Þöļîçý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_confirm_create_account">[βý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝŕéé ţö ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé, ţĥé Ĝööĝļé ÞŕîVåçý Þöļîçý, åñð ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_confirm_create_account_more">"[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ḿåý åļšö ŕéçéîVé åñð îñšţåļļ ûþðåţéš åñð åþþš ƒŕöḿ Ĝööĝļé åñð ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ḿåñûƒåçţûŕéŕ. Šöḿé åþþš ḿåý ɓé ðöŵñļöåðéð åñð îñšţåļļéð îƒ ýöû çöñţîñûé, åñð ýöû çåñ ŕéḿöVé ţĥéḿ öŕ åðĵûšţ ţĥéîŕ þéŕḿîššîöñš åţ åñý ţîḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="choose_account_type_title">[Çĥööšé åççöûñţ ţýþé one two three]</string>
    <string name="choose_account_title">[Çĥööšé åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="add_account_button_label">[Åðð ñéŵ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_error_passwords_dont_match">"[Ţĥé þåššŵöŕðš ðöñ'ţ ḿåţçĥ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_password_too_short">[Šĥöŕţ þåššŵöŕðš åŕé éåšý ţö ĝûéšš. Ţŕý öñé ŵîţĥ åţ ļéåšţ 8 çĥåŕåçţéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="account_error_password_too_weak">[Çöḿḿöñ ŵöŕðš åŕé éåšý ţö ĝûéšš. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_error_username_has_unsupported_characters">[Öñļý ļéţţéŕš (å–ž), ñûḿɓéŕš (0–9) åñð þéŕîöðš (.) åŕé åļļöŵéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="account_error_username_too_long">[Ýöûŕ ûšéŕñåḿé îš ļîḿîţéð ţö 30 çĥåŕåçţéŕš. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_error_username_too_short">[Ýöûŕ ûšéŕñåḿé ḿûšţ çöñţåîñ åţ ļéåšţ 6 çĥåŕåçţéŕš. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="account_error_recovery_email_invalid">"[Ţýþé å Våļîð éḿåîļ åððŕéšš.
Éхåḿþļé: ɓŕûçé@éхåḿþļé.çöḿ one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_username_choice_unavailable_title">"[%1$s îš ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé.
Ţŕý åñöţĥéŕ ûšéŕñåḿé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_creation_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ çŕéåţé åççöûñţ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_sign_in_failure_title">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šîĝñ îñ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_sign_in_failure_description">"[Ýöûŕ ûšéŕñåḿé åñð þåššŵöŕð ðöñ'ţ ḿåţçĥ. Þļéåšé Véŕîƒý ţĥéḿ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_second_device_failure_description">[Ţĥéŕé ŵåš å þŕöɓļéḿ šîĝñîñĝ îñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý. Çåñçéļ ţö ţŕý öţĥéŕ ḿéţĥöðš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="account_desc_confirm_sign_in">[βý šîĝñîñĝ îñ, ýöû åŕé åĝŕééîñĝ ţö ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé, Ĝööĝļé ÞŕîVåçý Þöļîçý, åñð Åððîţîöñåļ Ţéŕḿš öƒ ŠéŕVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="account_signing_in">[Šîĝñîñĝ îñ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_creating_account">[Çŕéåţîñĝ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_success">[Šûççéšš one two]</string>
    <string name="account_back">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="account_sign_in_with_google">[Šîĝñ îñ ţö ýöûŕ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_sign_in">[Šîĝñ îñ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_sign_in_with_password">[Ûšé ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_dont_sign_in">"[Ðöñ'ţ šîĝñ îñ one two]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_connectivity_lost">[Ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîVîţý ļöšţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_wifi_setup">[Ĝö ţö Ŵî-ƒî šéţûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_otp_confirm_title">[Åļḿöšţ ţĥéŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="account_otp_confirm_description">[Ýöûŕ åççöûñţ åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ ŕéQûîŕéš åñöţĥéŕ šîĝñ-îñ šţéþ ƒöŕ éхţŕå šéçûŕîţý. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="account_otp_title">[Šîĝñ îñ one two]</string>
    <string name="account_otp_description">[Ýöûŕ åççöûñţ åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ ŕéQûîŕéš åñöţĥéŕ šîĝñ-îñ šţéþ ƒöŕ éхţŕå šéçûŕîţý. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="account_captcha_request_title">"[ÞŕöVé ýöû'ŕé ñöţ å ŕöɓöţ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_captcha_request_description">[Föŕ šéçûŕîţý ŕéåšöñš, þļéåšé éñţéŕ ţĥé ţéхţ ðîšþļåýéð ɓéļöŵ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="account_summary_title">"[Ýöû'ŕé šîĝñéð îñ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="account_summary_description">[Ţĥé Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ \"%1$s\" îš šîĝñéð îñ. Ţĥîš çåñ ɓé çĥåñĝéð îñ Šéţţîñĝš öñçé šéţûþ îš çöḿþļéţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="account_sss_in_progress_title">[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé îš çöññéçţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_sss_in_progress_description_phone">[Çöñţîñûé šîĝñîñĝ îñ öñ ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðéVîçé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_sss_in_progress_description_computer">[Çöñţîñûé šîĝñîñĝ îñ öñ ýöûŕ çöḿþûţéŕ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_sss_in_progress_description">[Çöñţîñûé šîĝñîñĝ îñ öñ ýöûŕ öţĥéŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_second_device_title">[νîšîţ %1$s one two]</string>
    <string name="account_second_device_description">[βé šûŕé ţö çöññéçţ ýöûŕ þĥöñé öŕ ļåþţöþ ţö ţĥé šåḿé ñéţŵöŕķ åš ýöûŕ %1$s. Ţĥéñ éñţéŕ ţĥîš çöðé: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="account_second_device_code_description">[%1$s]</string>
    <string name="account_web_auth_title">[Šîĝñ îñ öñ ţĥé ŵéɓ one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_web_auth_description">[Ýöû çåñ ûšé ţĥé ŵéɓ ţö ļöĝ îñţö ýöûŕ åççöûñţ öŕ çŕéåţé å ñéŵ öñé. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="url_load_unsuccessful_message">"[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé îšñ'ţ çöññéçţéð ţö ţĥé Îñţéŕñéţ. Ţö Vîéŵ ţĥîš îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ ñöŵ, ĝö ţö %s îñ å ŵéɓ ɓŕöŵšéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="main_title">[Ĝööĝļé one two]</string>
    <string name="caption_email">[Éñţéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ éḿåîļ åððŕéšš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="password_hint">[Þåššŵöŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="show_password">[Šĥöŵ þåššŵöŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="success">[Šûççéšš¡ one two]</string>
    <string name="caption_password">[Éñţéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ þåššŵöŕð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="submit">[Šûɓḿîţ one two]</string>
    <string name="title_get_token">[Ĝéţţîñĝ Ţöķéñ one two]</string>
    <string name="title_grant_cred">[Ţĥîš åþþ ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö one two three]</string>
    <string name="template_permission_item">"[• ^1 
 one]"</string>
    <string name="title_sync_data">[Šţåŕţîñĝ šýñçîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="location_opt_int_title">[Ļöçåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="location_opt_int_overview">"[Ļéţ Ĝööĝļé åñð ţĥîŕð þåŕţý åþþš ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ þéŕḿîššîöñ ûšé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="usage_and_diag_opt_int_title">[Ĥéļþ îḿþŕöVé Åñðŕöîð Ţν one two three]</string>
    <string name="usage_and_diag_opt_int_overview">"[Ĥéļþ îḿþŕöVé ýöûŕ Åñðŕöîð Ţν ɓý åûţöḿåţîçåļļý šéñðîñĝ ðîåĝñöšţîç åñð ûšåĝé ðåţå ţö Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ ŵöñ'ţ ɓé ûšéð ţö îðéñţîƒý ýöû åñð ĥéļþš ţéåḿš ŵöŕķîñĝ öñ ţĥîñĝš ļîķé åþþ þéŕƒöŕḿåñçé åñð ñéŵ Ĝööĝļé ƒéåţûŕéš. Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé åţ ĥţţþ://ĝ.çö/ÅñðŕöîðÛšåĝéĤéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two]"</string>
    <string name="usage_and_diag_opt_settings_title">[Ûšåĝé &amp; Ðîåĝñöšţîçš one two three]</string>
    <string name="auth_login_activity_loginfail_text_pwonly">[Ýöû ţýþéð åñ îñçöŕŕéçţ þåššŵöŕð öŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ ĥåš çĥåñĝéð. Ŕé-ţýþé ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð. Îƒ ýöû ƒöŕĝöţ ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð åñð ñééð ţö ŕéçöVéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ çļîçķ <annotation id="help_url">ĥéŕé</annotation>. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="auth_error_invalid_second_factor">[Ûšé åñ åþþ-šþéçîƒîç þåššŵöŕð îñšţéåð öƒ ýöûŕ ŕéĝûļåŕ åççöûñţ þåššŵöŕð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="auth_error_account_not_verified">"[Ţĥîš åççöûñţ ĥåšñ'ţ ɓééñ Véŕîƒîéð. Çĥéçķ ýöûŕ éḿåîļ åñð ƒöļļöŵ ţĥé îñçļûðéð ļîñķ ţö Véŕîƒý ţĥîš åççöûñţ. 

(Ţö ŕéçöVéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, ĝö ţö ĥţţþ://ŵŵŵ.ĝööĝļé.çöḿ/åççöûñţš/ŕéçöVéŕý öñ ýöûŕ çöḿþûţéŕ.) one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="auth_error_account_disabled">"[Ţĥîš åççöûñţ ĥåš ɓééñ ðîšåɓļéð. 

(Föŕ ðéţåîļš, Vîšîţ ĥţţþ://ĝööĝļé.çöḿ/åççöûñţš ŵîţĥ å ŵéɓ ɓŕöŵšéŕ.) one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="auth_account_already_has_gmail">[Åççöûñţ åļŕéåðý ĥåš Ĝḿåîļ. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="auth_error_bad_password">[Ţĥé þåššŵöŕð îš ţöö ŵéåķ öŕ çöñţåîñš îñVåļîð çĥåŕåçţéŕš. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="auth_error_bad_username">[ÎñVåļîð ûšéŕñåḿé. one two three]</string>
    <string name="auth_error_login_failed">"[Ýöûŕ ûšéŕñåḿé åñð þåššŵöŕð ðöñ'ţ ḿåţçĥ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ.

Ţö ŕéçöVéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ îñƒö, ĝö ţö ĝööĝļé.çöḿ/åççöûñţš/ŕéçöVéŕý/. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="auth_error_not_logged_in">"[Ûšéŕ îšñ'ţ šîĝñéð îñ. one two three]"</string>
    <string name="auth_doesnt_use_gmail">[ <b>^1</b>" ðöéšñ'ţ ûšé Ĝḿåîļ.  one two three]"</string>
    <string name="auth_error_username_unavailable">"[Ûšéŕñåḿé îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé. one two three]"</string>
    <string name="auth_plus_failure_text">"[Ýöûŕ ŕéQûéšţ ţö ĵöîñ Ĝööĝļé+ ðîðñ'ţ ĝö ţĥŕöûĝĥ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ ƒŕöḿ åñý ŵéɓ ɓŕöŵšéŕ åţ þļûš.ĝööĝļé.çöḿ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="auth_invalid_scope">[Åûţĥéñţîçåţîöñ éŕŕöŕ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="require_sign_in_title">[Þļéåšé šîĝñ îñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="require_sign_in_description">[Å çĥåñĝé îñ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ ŕéQûîŕéš ţĥåţ ýöû šîĝñ îñ åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="already_signed_in_error">[Ţĥîš åççöûñţ åļŕéåðý éхîšţš öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé one two three four five]</string>
</resources>
